It's 12:47. Thirteen minutes to class.
And I'm seven people deep
in the canteen line.
Twenty people shouting orders.
Paper chits. Cash.
A kitchen ten feet away
that can't hear a word.
A samosa is not worth
a debarred semester.
And the owner? Two bad choices.
Drown in cash and paper every rush...
or hand 15 to 30% to the delivery apps.
Commission they can't afford.
This is Tray.
Shopify for campus canteens.
A non-technical owner logs in once —
and instantly gets their canteen, online.
Admin console, kitchen view, own domain.
No code. No agency. No developers.
Students pick a canteen, see live menus
with prep times,
and pay by U-P-I — a single-use QR.
Place the order.
Watch it go from Placed,
to Preparing, to Ready.
Pick up with a four-digit O-T-P.
In the kitchen, the ticket just appears.
Incoming, preparing, ready —
then verify the O-T-P. About 300ms.
And the owner sees everything —
a live activity feed, every order,
across every canteen on campus.
One dashboard.
Zero percent commission — money settles
straight to each canteen's bank via Razorpay.
Tenants are isolated in Postgres
row-level security:
worst case is zero rows,
never a leaked one.
Two students, one last samosa?
Only one charge goes through. By design.
The line dissolves. Students stop
waiting and start eating.
In our testing, that's about
12 minutes back — every single lunch.
Tray. Zero commission. No code.
And the lunch line disappears.